Welcome home. Your name is right here.
My name is Lucifer, son of the Morningstar, and bearer of the first dawn is my destiny.
Beef jerky sure looks good, doesn't it, Jimmy?
Look at that with his herbal cigarettes.
Why not just slip it in your pants? Who's going to know?
It's like taking beef jerky from a baby.
Or in this case, a convenience store.
And you're in and out before that pesky angel
even got a word in edge wise.
What I miss.
Too little, too late.
Goody two shoes.
Ha, ha, ha, what on this?
More like everything, stupid angel.
Sh, what?
It's easy when you remember these simple steps.
Just use the acronym, 10th, firsts, team.
Teleport. E. Evaluate. This guy wants that jerky, but he doesn't have the money. M.P. Make a plan.
I'm gonna tell this guy to put that jerky in his pants. Tee again. Tell the plan. Put that jerky in your pants.
You. Upsell.
Hey, wouldn't it be fun to bind, torture, and kill that guy?
That way you have all the jerky you want and that beer.
We'll get them next time.
Oh, remember to always stay on the right shoulder,
which is the left shoulder.
The correct shoulder is the left.
The right shoulder is the angel's domain.
But you're on the right shoulder.
Ah, ah, ah, D.T.
Do not talk to the angel.
I'm going to be as stubborn as good times, but I won't ever stop missing simply that sweepy for over an hour
No, no
Grandpa's is retired. I haven't made a naughty list in over 20 years
I tried to get them gum for nickel to follow in my footsteps
This one isn't interested unless it's a horn to curve.
It's a horn to villages of avalanches.
Because avalanches come for nickel,
why do you think that the horn blast happens and then the snow falls?
Are you trying to warn them in the future?
Kids today every time they fart they get a trophy when they got rid of spanking
That's when the whole world went down the crapple and Satan agrees with you
Satan needs me to keep the children in line
The ones that are left
So what do you say are you interested in working with us on this fetch my drowning tub
Memphis is back!
Oh, great.
I don't like the dance, but I appreciate why you're doing it.
Workshop!
The other one's really strong.
Up for $24.99, you can get a package that includes an 8x10.
We just want to see Santa, right, Ethan?
Okay, go on, go see Santa.
Hey, Ethan, smile big for mommy.
You're just gonna lie to my face and stand here and take pictures with your cell phone.
Here you go.
Hello, Ethan Raikstra.
How old were we last night?
I know everything about you, young Ethan.
Come here. Sit on my bony, might-covered lap.
I know that you pee in the shower.
And I know that you broke your sister's iPad.
And you said it fell.
What's this shit?
You close the door, I can't see my son anymore.
If you pay for the package, you can get a video
and you'll see everything going on.
Why can't you just leave the door open?
It's gonna freak you out.
It's gonna what?
Come here. Come here baby.
It's too late for Ethan.
He's on the list.
That's the first kid today.
Where are all the children, I thought?
It's been a bit of a hard sell.
Yo, do you like that thing it is?
Do you like throwing those clothes?
Oh, uh.
There might be a few more.
I just don't want to, like,
Okay, this is a funny show. I think you'll eat this here. This is called the writer's retreat from hell, okay?
So if you like to eat like crampus, I love crampus. There's also a good American dad with crampus in it. It's a musical.
It's a retreat. Home sweet home, huh?
Get comfy and then we're gonna write the new Friday live. Revived and refried.
Troyes get the party started. Do we have any lime tree down in the basement? I'll be right back
You know, when Gary and I hatched this crazy idea to write a Friday Live script,
we decided we wanted to do something fresh and original,
but with that classic Rudy feeling.
So put your thinking caps on, just start throwing ideas at us.
See, as long as all the ideas take place with Rudy having access to a fryer,
so all the action of the film happens inside of a diner.
Okay, I think it could be maybe scarier if he like could leave the diner,
get out of his element and like see if he could get people.
No, Rudy lives in the diner. He lives behind the fryer.